Hey guys! What's Up!
This is Xiao Cai. Welcome to Xiao Cai Talk Show.
This is my first video, I do n’t know what to talk about,
Starting with the simplest, today we will talk about the mantra.
Think carefully, you often hear some mantras,
I have summarized something that I can often hear.
For example:"OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, whatever"
Like these perfunctory but not excessive rhetoric,
Almost everyone will say that both acquaintances and strangers will use it.
Just like:"‘ Is my food delicious? Okay. ’
‘Do you like spicy food? still alright'
"How about this movie?" Very good, okay '. "
Although not everyone answered this, it is certain that this is the answer of the vast majority of people,
A conclusion is drawn from this-
Anyone who puts words like "OK" on their lips
Must be an ordinary person.
You will definitely refute, what else can I say without saying "OK"?
You just talk about specific subjective feelings in a little more detail
Or objective evaluation is a hundred times stronger than saying "OK", ordinary people!
In fact, in previous street interviews,
Many passersby answered some ambiguous neutral words,
One mouth is ‘okay’ now gone, because
The people who cut the film also know that it is boring, so they cut it off.
Why do Chinese people like to say these euphemistic neutral words?
This is not only indescribable but also low-key.
I personally think,
It is because China has been under too much feudal rule since ancient times,
If you say something wrong, you will be killed.
Cause people's minds to be confined and dare not tell the truth
Anyway, obedient people live longer, and disobedient people die early. Every day kills chickens and monkeys,
Who dares to tell the truth?
So, all we can say is these ambiguous neutral words.
So it spread.
It can be accepted by most people, and it can only be unspeakable.
For example, the same word:"OK", the tone is different, the face is different,
The meaning of the expression will be exactly the opposite.
For example, I asked you, "Who do you think is beautiful?"
"You smile half blush and say:" OK "
That's what it means.
If I ask you, "Who do you think is ugly?",
You hummed and said, "OK",
That is what ugly means.
Why not say it directly, you have to guess.
I summed up the following reasons.
First of all, it may be that you have not thought about it or are embarrassed.
The second is to worry about leaks and gossip behind others.
The main thing I think is
Herd psychology that follows the mainstream and is assimilated.
People are like clouds, without learning.
Everyone says "okay", what you say is different from others,
Then we will reject you, who will tell you the truth. what?
Then, in order to cater to everyone, there will be someone who will become a raccoon dog and a crowd.
Realistic helplessness, sometimes have no choice.
But sometimes personality is also very important, such as invention,
If someone else has made something for a long time, you still imitate it, then you will always be a cottage.
As another example, when answering questions in class, others' answers are the same.
What you think is different from others, but you are afraid to say wrong,
You hesitated for a while, and finally answered the same views as others,
This loses personality.
Of course I say this, you may not feel the use of personality.
Let me give another extreme example,
For example, in the historical Nanjing Massacre, three devils watched a group of people,
No one dares to resist.
Of course, if I pointed a gun at my head, I might not dare to resist,
I can scare urine.
But I was all about to die. It was a knife horizontally and a knife vertically.
Why don't you go all out?
But no one resists, why should I resist?
Why should I be a dead ghost? Die together!
At this time, if more personalized people can go out shopping,
Maybe this group of people could be saved.
But no one would do this,
I think it's okay.
Okay, we will talk here today. See you next time. Bye 👋
If you like my video, please remember to like and share the message, and turn on the small bell by the way, sa ~.
Come take a look at our team,
This is light, this is photography,
This is the director, this is the actor,
this is
Background
This is the late stage, this is the special effect
This is a screenwriter
He is still one
Honest honest man