Hey, What's Up! This is Xiao Cai. Welcome to my channel!
Congratulations, you have been tricked in
I didn’t teach you to surf the net
You see the title, you know, this is a debate, I’m doing a speech
To be honest, it’s kind of sad to overturn the wall
Because the Internet that should have been freely accessed in mainland China
Being constantly blocked, only the internal network is allowed inside the wall.
Many people don’t even notice the existence of the wall
So why do we come over the wall and go online scientifically, are we free?
If you want to go to the extranet and go abroad, you can’t do it. It’s the same for Hong Kong, Macau and Taiwan.
But there is no money. In addition to the difficulty of accessing the Internet in China, other things are very convenient.
Can you use the intranet without going to the extranet?
No, if the intranet is easy to use, who would struggle to access the extranet?
That Baidu is really a copycat.
Soulai search is all water stickers, no matter how advanced search
Filtering search is still a water sticker, or it’s a lie
Google is the same sometimes, but there are not so many restrictions
Higher accuracy, you can also watch small yellow films
So this is very sad, one of the most distant distances in the world is the disconnection
Why do you want to block the network? Take the old road of clearing the government's closed door?
This involves a lot of sensitive topics. We are physically inside the wall and we can’t tell the truth.
On the mainland, we are not qualified to talk about politics
Otherwise, it’s easy to get caught
That's the legendary drink tea, check the water meter and the like
Even threatens family members, so these sensitive issues
Just have a heart in your heart and live your little life
And most of those who dare to tell the truth are over the wall physically
That is to emigrate overseas
Those who didn’t physically turn over the wall, were caught as soon as they told the truth, and even broke their families
So I dare not say it, dare to speak without anger, admit to counseling, hold it down if you are not convinced, and try to lie down with your salary.
Over the wall, there are two main categories
One is over the wall, the other is over the wall.
Spiritually turning the wall is at the technical level, breaking through the network blockade and cyber attacks
Of course, this is a protracted battle, not to say that it is once and for all
All those titles that say permanently over the wall are all deceiving CTR
The spirit relies on technology, of course, the technology is not enough, the money comes together
Nodes built by yourself will often be blocked soon, and it works in the first two years
Now it is blocked as soon as it is built, and it cannot withstand firewall attacks at all
It takes a lot of time and energy to resurrect
Continuous self-maintenance, can't afford to play, but also very tired
You can only buy someone else's airport
Of course it’s not that someone’s airport will not be blocked
Someone in the background is maintaining, and if they are blocked, they will be unblocked.
Seal one solution, one solution one, one solution one.
We haven't done backstage yet
What is the equivalent of building a node and maintaining a node?
Driving and repairing the car, I'm willing to drive the car, I don't want to repair it if it's broken
I have to find someone else to do it, and I am not incapable of doing it, but it is time-consuming and exhausting.
Not necessarily good repairs, or even bad repairs.
Those people who are unwilling to do their jobs will spawn a type of work, that is, those who sell airports
I’ll just spend some money and save some time, otherwise I will spend all day on repairing the car
How tired I can't do anything
How to update the method of turning over the wall, nothing more than two agreements, one is SOCKS, the other is VMess
The SSR you use is a batch of SOCKS5 nodes, which is the airport.
The V2ray and Trojan you use are all VMess plus some DIY encryption modes
Everyone knows the mainstream way, but it’s not as powerful as the legend
Like what ws+tls+web, https traffic disguised as mainland, looks seamless
But in the end, it will still be seen through the wall and then blocked, but it is relatively longer and the cost of resurrection is lower.
But the technical cost is high, the operating cost is high
Are you willing to drive, and are you willing to repair the car?
What's more, it can sometimes be as complicated as building a car! Why bother?
If you have enough time, just toss yourself. Anyway, I was completely exhausted.
Anyway, the wall will not be demolished in the first half, so I can only seek the redemption of Xiao Shenke in this network prison.
Of course, spiritual overturning does not mean spiritual freedom
I’m talking about those who are patriotic over the wall
He thinks it's right to block the network, he will not blame those who make firewalls
He feels well controlled, at least invisible
He feels that most of the world outside the wall is reactionary, and there are many traitors
With the wall, you can shield out the dirty things he doesn’t want to see, at least not seeing is clean
Even if there is blood flowing outside and corpses are raging across the field, it's a matter of my care. Am I in charge?
Most people think this way, for people like us who look angry
They are not saved, in turn, for them, we are abandon
We are not saved
We will only be treated as brainwashed by reactionary remarks
What should I do? Don’t talk about politics, you should eat, drink, drink
Pretend to be deaf and dumb
Anyway, some big truths can only be suffocated, and rotten in my heart
Anyway, it's useless to say it, only to be regarded as a lunatic
After talking about the mental over the wall, let's talk about the physical over the wall
I’m an immigrant if I’m physically over the wall.
It stands to reason that after going abroad, you can accept some free and open new ideas
But the reality is often the opposite, overseas pinks are also everywhere
I remember an overseas student who said he wanted to oppose freedom of speech and was scolded by a group of people
How do you deal with this little overseas pink? I just want to shoot him, forgive him for being a god
We are only responsible for sending him to God
You must be thinking in your heart, the United States is so chaotic, why should I go abroad?
Free, Americans live like the end of the world
Have you ever considered why you can only see the negative news of the United States in China
There is not a little positive news
You don’t even see people sponsoring poor people in the country and doing charity
In China, I can only see what the ban is on the evaluation of the African currency, and follow him to fight together
Xi Jinping's name is right, no comments are allowed
It’s the same in the United States, where you can’t see positive news about China and prohibit China’s rise.
Pressed Huawei hard and let him get out
Why should there be malicious competition, what is the picture?
I don’t tell you, you know, when the world’s boss chants
For example, the gang boss has a second-in-command who wants to usurp
Once found, he will be killed sooner or later
But these leaders are not vegetarian, he also has countermeasures
Let others catch the handle
Isn't that the competition of big powers?
To brainwash the people of their own country, only praise and no criticism
It’s like a domestic social software, only like, no step
You don’t want to suffocate, or get out
This kind of big power competition is all about scams, you die
I am dead, you are happy, you are dead, I am happy, I want to set off fireworks
In a word, sooner or later, the other party will be killed, but this is a long process
There will always be some ambiguous interest exchanges in the middle, that is, dirty transactions
To make an analogy, I originally grabbed you
To whip you with a whip, fan you with ear scrapers, but you have money
Gave me a million and wanted me to let you go
I'm not stupid, let you go, don't you find someone to get revenge?
But I'm greedy for money, and I'll collect it when I give it, so I won't worry about the debt
You have given money, then I won’t beat you, but I can’t help but let you go
Isn't it important that the interests of major powers are exchanged?
Go back and talk about the principle of overturning the wall
No matter how advanced the technology of turning over the wall is
Don’t you just change IP? You seal one and I change one
You might say that some over-the-wall technology can ignore the firewall, so that the firewall cannot detect abnormal traffic
You think about it carefully
Overturning the wall permanently, ignoring the firewall, but after a while, he began to hit his face
Did you start a tutorial on permanently turning over the wall again?
If it is permanent, is it not enough for you to post a video? right?
Besides the firewall, no matter how updated its technology is, how to strengthen the attack
Isn’t it all the same? Seal IP, you change one, I seal one
People over the wall are not vegetarian. You can block my IP and I will be able to revive the IP. Who is afraid of who!
I feel uncomfortable without crossing the wall
When will this endless war, which is one foot tall and one demon tall, be over?
Probably in October this year, it is said that the United States is spending huge sums of money to demolish the wall!
I didn't want to believe this kind of thing at first, why wouldn't I do it earlier if I could demolish the wall?
The ghost knows what's going on?
But now I don’t want to believe it, I have to give myself a hint of hope and comfort myself with chicken broth
There is also Musk, not Marx, of course it is similar
Musk, his small company, puts satellites to play every day, and dozens of small satellites go up,
Just make the space around the earth the same as the dump, the artificial satellite has a very short life span
Less than two or three years, more than ten years, to put it plainly, it is all garbage
Everyone sitting here is trash
What can these satellites do? Engage in the star chain project, put the earth in a fishing net
This is not a new concept. Organizations that can launch satellites are thinking about how to trap the earth.
It’s just a matter of money. If you send one, anyone can send it, and I can send it.
Thousands of satellites are distributed, there are not so rich organizations
Including Musk’s company, not so much money
However, if there is no money, there is a cheaper way
Basically, 400 to 600 satellites can barely operate a star chain project
Once it works, the firewall can't stop it
Because you can connect to WiFi without the operator's signal tower, but you need a receiving base station
It's similar to watching satellite TV in the past
It will definitely be regulated at that time, prohibiting the connection of Musk’s WiFi
And Musk in order to allow the mainland to connect to WiFi
It may be bought by the government, which means that the external network you connect to is a filtered external network
Generally speaking, it is much better than before, at least no wall-over tool
Remember the WiFi balloon project developed by Google in previous years?
It is still in full swing!
The WiFi balloon developed by Google aims to connect remote areas to the Internet
At present, Sri Lanka has fully covered WiFi balloons
Compared with laying a lot of optical fiber, it is indeed a lot more money saving
However, they can’t enter China, they are under government control, and don’t put WiFi balloons.
If the government agrees, the area of ​​WiFi covered by a balloon is about 40 square kilometers
To cover the entire continent, many balloons are needed
The life span of this kind of balloon is not long, that is more than three months
Remove the old one and replace it with a new one
This kind of balloon is a helium balloon, not a hot air balloon
An antenna is also needed to connect to WiFi, which looks like a lollipop
It really doesn't work in China
However, with Google's exclusion from China, the project is progressing smoothly
Currently island countries like New Zealand and Australia
Some of the remote areas above have basically covered almost
In fact, this kind of balloon is suitable for connecting to the island
If I bought a small island and didn’t have a network, to connect to the Internet, I had to connect with a submarine cable
If my island is a very remote island in the Pacific Ocean
It’s not realistic, let Google put a balloon
Crossing the wall is a kind of sorrow, it is a national shame
It imprisons more than one billion Chinese people in invisible prisons
It imprisoned not criminals, but countless free souls
If you have a prison, you want to escape from prison.
Quite tragic, but the reality is often the opposite
I feel that most people don’t care if they are imprisoned in an invisible prison
They think they are alive and well, they just have enough to eat, not so much thought
So, it’s all deserved to be blunt, even when leeks deserve to be harvested
You might say that it is because of the firewall that China can become a world power
That's right, the wall at the head. This strength is based on the fool and the weak
Am i right
If you like my video, please remember to share it and turn on the small bell!
See you next time, bye!