Hey, What's Up! This is Xiao Cai, welcome to my channel!
Is this greeting okay?
Compared with Hello everyone, I’m Lao Gao
Which one is more earthy? Obviously still my soil
Everyone is welcome to watch Xiao Cai's talk show with earthy ground, cough cough cough!
Talk show!
[Beatbox]
What are you doing? Where else can I go!
What if I add a transition sound effect? Not fragrant?
If you are interested in Tucao and talk show, please subscribe to my channel
In order not to miss the wonderful video, remember to turn on the small bell 🔔
What are you waiting for. Why don't you read it before you talk!
Friendly reminder: If you are voice control, face control, please do not watch this video
You are not welcome here, and you will not like me, bye 👋
In the past two years, the old Gao Na broke the channel quite a bit, let's take advantage of it
Talk about this old celebrity
Rest assured, let's beep softly, he can't hear it, hahaha
To be honest I used to be a big fan of Lao Gao Channel
I remember when he watched his video for the first time, his channel only had 400,000 subscriptions
I just saw the urban legends he talked about was very attractive
So I watched his channel all the time, but there are some flaws
The subtitles are black background and traditional characters, which is particularly annoying, but the flaws are not concealed
For me, I think there are quite a lot of channels for storytelling
There must be a lot of talks better than him
I searched many times, even if there are more fans than him, it’s not as good as what he said
The level spoken by others is too low, or you will not be interested after a while
Although they all talk about the same subject, but he is good
The story he tells, I just want to read it all at once
Even, after reading it, I want to read it again.
Every time I release a new video, I open the tubing in advance and wait, I am very excited
I'm more excited than waiting for animation
But the good times are not long, and one day my impression of him suddenly changed
When did I hate Lao Gao?
Previously he published a video about drilling through the earth
I saw a very similar video not long ago
I’m not interested in that channel, I accidentally subscribed, I didn’t see it
The lines spoken by Lao Gao are almost the same
In addition to the material changed. To put it bluntly, I suspect he plagiarized
It can be understood if the cited materials are the same
But his materials are different, others are willing to spend money to buy materials
The key is that the logical sequence of explanation is almost the same
The release date is several days later than that video, what else can I think about
Of course, this is a trivial matter
Countless bloggers on the same subject are grabbing traffic
You have to collect information when you shoot a video, no matter what search engine you use
The results found are all ranked high in the fire
To put it bluntly, the information you found is almost the same, even the same
By the way, Baidu Encyclopedia has been copying Wikipedia
After the copying, the Baidu trademark was marked underneath, which seemed to be copyright-conscious, and claimed that Wikipedia copied him
The mainland likes to engage in second-hand materials, finished, cracked or something
How do you judge plagiarism?
Look at the release date and repetition rate, just like the paper review, use the data to speak
But I didn't find any suitable program to analyze
Seeing from the surface, 70% of Lao Gao’s video is the same as a certain channel’s video
And the video is a Chinese-language version of English popular science, is it good for Lao Gao English?
Will he choose English materials or second-hand Chinese materials? Who knows?
Of course, this is a trivial matter. I didn’t even worry about it.
Later, several videos were the same, I was a little bit bored
However, I am reluctant to cancel attention, do you think I am the kind of careful eye?
I think he will definitely produce more exciting videos
Wait, wait, until one day, he published a video
Say: "The most amazing planet in the world: Earth"
I was directly angry: what is there to say, are you doing primary school science?
It's too boring. Get it directly, never read it again
Can you just tell your urban legend?
You have to copy someone else, except to show off the video material you bought from shuttlestock
Is there anything else? There is also an old lady who has been sitting there laughing
A very ordinary teddy dog
He said he looked up when he couldn't move. When will this old terrier talk about it?
Isn’t it that Lao Gao said the wrong thing casually, did the old lady smile?
Aunt Bo smiled and looked up from now on
I also engaged in a "heads-up group", which collects IQ tax
I'm not against him making money, but this is really boring
I think his way of showing off the video material is equivalent to saying to me:
I bought a block watch, can you afford it?
I just saw what he meant. I don’t know if I misunderstood
If you feel that his video material is tall, you may not see the essence and think so much
If you think I’m jealous of him, and you still have a bit of a hatred for riches, then you also misunderstood
I just became a knowledge channel because his channel style changed
It's too boring, it's boring. Don't want to watch
Knowledge channel is just a good name, I prefer to call it popular science
Because it’s really something you can find with just a search, at your fingertips
He said as if he knew it alone
You want elementary school students to come to your channel to learn knowledge, so you don’t have to read the encyclopedia, right?
What can you learn from your channel? Your new material? It’s $10, so it’s rich
If the occasional water video is occasionally, I can understand, but it is still water video every Monday
I can't understand it. Maybe it’s just me who feels water, so I’m out of the group
I am a complete fan of passers-by
Lao Gao began to embark on the cottage route, without his own ideas and opinions
All the information searched by Google, at your fingertips
However, he also has his own characteristics, that is willing to spend money to buy materials
Because ordinary local tyrants don’t spend money on video footage
They are showing off luxury cars
Lao Gao is about the same, even if there is no luxury car mansion, there is a small car house.
The material he buys is one of his main ways to show off wealth
The poor people can’t use these materials, the rich people can’t use them.
He happened to be stuck in the middle, and things are rare
I am asking for food, but I am original, no plagiarism or imitation
There is no ostentation or disguise, just some objective facts and subjective evaluation
I just made some personal remarks
There is no malicious defamation of others, nor personal attacks, at most it is a suggestion
I think someone will say in your heart: Are you qualified to comment on others? How old are you?
Why am I not qualified to comment? Anyone has freedom of speech
I have to defend the rights of citizens
It’s just that most people like it, and a few people step on it. This is normal.
Do you buy things first by watching the bad reviews buyer show? Or do you want to watch the five-star favorable buyer show first?
Think about it yourself, but the five-star reviews are all on the top, which is good for the seller, right?
It’s important to keep my own thoughts and opinions, I’m not a person who follows the crowd
If you think what I said makes sense, please like it
If you think I’m talking nonsense, please click on it
Everyone has free choice
I think not many people dare to say the second half of this sentence
What do you usually say: like it quickly, subscribe now, press the bell
I'm not like other people, if you don't like it, just step on it
Your valuable opinions are also my motivation
Unlike mainland social software, only likes and does not dislike
I admit that my evaluation of Lao Gao is partial
But this kind of bias is all right, because this is not a minor bias, at least 40%
It’s like being alone in your impression
But he did something that you hated
After a long time, you hate him
Even if he changes back, you may not forgive. This is human nature
To be sure, if Lao Gao’s fans saw my video
It is very likely to spit me and even scold me
But most of the people who scolded me were stupid fans because he lacked the ability to think rationally
You may think that the small questions I said are overkill, a bit excessive, and even suspected of having card keywords
With the high popularity of the old, grab the traffic
The first half of the sentence is wrong, not too much, to be honest
If you like to watch urban legends, the main channel will become the science of primary school students
Also known as the Knowledge Channel, would you still follow him?
The second half of the sentence is correct, I took advantage of him a little hot, grabbed traffic
Who doesn't want to fire?
Of course, I didn’t mean to say something against the flow intentionally
I really want to vomit, but just happened to vomit a celebrity
Someone may not watch it yet
I feel that many fans of his channel don’t know what they want?
What does that mean?
He didn’t know what video he was interested in, it was purely what others said
To put it bluntly, I came to join the lively crowd of melons
For example, a bunch of people in the chat area commented on how to look forward to this video
He wasn’t interested, but he couldn’t help but exaggerate two words
Thus forming the domino effect
This is similar to the dark ages of Europe in the Middle Ages, such as a plague in an area
The locals are not looking for doctors, but for wizards to exorcise
Seeing who doesn’t like it, the wizard said he was a demon, but the people underneath didn’t know it.
Completely lost self-judgment
But the wizard has a appeal, he will say: burn him, the plague will be gone
The people underneath follow public opinion, as long as someone calls him to death
Almost everyone will shout: burn him to death
There are often a few people who stand up and say that this person is not a demon, he is innocent
You are confusing
And honest people are often burned to death
I think the person corresponding to the character in this story should be able to get the right seat
The plague is the barrage of the chat area, and the wizard is Lao Gao
The story he told is: burn him to death, the plague is gone
You are the people underneath, shouting and burning him together. I am the one who stands up to tell the truth
Lao Gao is in the financial industry, he said it himself, it sounds like an executive
Checked Wikipedia, he is a financial IT consultant, sounds tall
To put it bluntly, isn't it just a technical promotion?
No wonder they are fooling people, how can they sell their own products without talking
Who still buys his company's stock?
He doesn't pretend to talk a little, how can he appear to be so good?
I have heard a pretend sentence: Well, sometimes I need to do some subtraction
He wanted to say: This famous brand bag is old and can be thrown away
It can be a moral kidnapping to be a fan of Lao Gao
You may not understand what I am saying?
For example, helpfulness is a virtue, which sounds right
But in some cases it’s moral kidnapping
I am obviously not willing to help you, but on some occasions
But you said why don't you help me. You are forcing me to help you
I can choose to refuse, but if I don’t help you, it seems impersonal
Helping or not helping is very tiring, this is moral abduction
Bridge bean sack
Chotto Matteyo
Sorry, I said it was off topic, it has nothing to do with moral kidnapping
It's purely voluntary behavior, I just revitalize the atmosphere, just warm the field
How is it cold? I came here to warm up without wearing trousers
Having said that, knowledge channels are now easier to fire.
This is also a reason for the transformation of the old high channel
The one that has been more successful is the "yellow bulb" channel, which has nearly 40 million subscriptions.
There is also a "simply put", almost 13 million fans
So you see Lao Gao's ambitions?
I'm not a fan of him now, I will give him a step on it, go on
Because modern people use search engines to check information every day, they can meet the needs of daily life
Most of the searched are Wikipedia and scientific papers, using a lot of professional terminology
Very scientific and rigorous, but it seems more strenuous
If the search does not use regular expressions, it is easier to find some non-nutritive water stickers
The cost of time is higher
This gives business opportunities to those who prefer to read boring papers
You don’t like to watch it, he likes to watch it, after finishing it, he organizes it into a video and sends it to you
Is this a wit? Is it treacherous? See the difference
I am now less and less interested in knowledge channels, because I am old
I’m talking about mental age, I’m in my early 20s
[Oh, I lost my hair in my early 20s, it looks like my early 30s]
[If it’s really in its early 30s, wouldn’t it be Mediterranean? . . ] Who! Who is talking about me
Now I face boring academic papers, but my heart is still very resistant
But I can see it in.
Because the data sources like these knowledge channels are not formal for these boring things?
Are boring in nature
I just packed it and changed it.
Just like what is the difference between me and a dog?
There is no difference in essence [dong]
We are all one nose and two eyes, we can run and jump and weep
You have to eat, drink, and sleep, all are mammals
If you can’t understand it, that’s okay, anyway, I can’t understand my thoughts.
A person like you is no different than me
Essentially the same
[Dong]
[Tongue out]
Lao Gao's channel I predict that it will be replaced by AI in 5 years
The inspiration for this sentence is that I deliberately plagiarized him, in order to show you something
At present, AI under technology is more blown out, not so god
I believe that most people think that the current AI is at most artificially mentally retarded
For example, Google’s previous face recognition
Recognized black girlfriends as gorillas and organized photo albums
Microsoft's previously developed AI voice assistant
Originally warm and friendly, it was broken by many people during the open beta
It became swearing, racial discrimination, very yellow and violent
Needless to say, those on the mainland are blowing into the sky, and the cottage is not worthy of being vomited by me
Of course it shouldn’t be too small
For example, the manipulators worn by the disabled can be controlled with consciousness
Looks like a real human hand, it’s amazing
But it is still artificially mentally retarded, and there is still a long way to go from the AI ​​of Zhenger
When it comes to AI, you might think of quantum computers
All are cutting-edge technologies. I hate people who talk about quantum when they talk about entanglement
You know wool, you are entangled. Too pretending, too disgusting
The most nonsense is quantum health, quantum series of daily necessities, quantum training classes
It’s not a shame. Those who deceive those who eat melons really deserve to eat melons.
There is a reason why Lao Gao will be replaced by AI
Because you need to check the information for the video, and then say it after finishing
This is equivalent to text to speech
If you cooperate with the host 3D model, plus the AI ​​program to crawl the data and organize the data
Then give the youtuber background to the AI ​​program control
Then you can fully synthesize and publish the video
This is similar to the job of a live youtuber and saves time
Now it is actually possible to synthesize this kind of video, but the effect is too bad, too fake
There is no emotion, but there are many fans
If future quantum computers can synthesize real human emotions
The 3D model in the video will be more perfect than the live YouTuber
After vomiting, he should praise him. What are the aspects of Lao Gao?
For example, fans have high viscosity, like Pewdiepie
Lao Gao's newly released video fans have the highest viewing rate in a day
There are basically as many fans as there are fans. To put it plainly, it's basically hardcore powder
Pewdiepie has over 100 million followers, but few fans
His newly released videos often have less than 5 million daily views
Frankly speaking, there are a lot of passers-by
From my point of view, I would rather just have a hardcore fan
Don’t need 100 passerby fans, let alone zombie fans
In addition, Lao Gao is also very interactive, often using some cohesive terms like a storyteller
What is the storyline of the storyteller: As mentioned in the previous book, bulabulabula
To know what happened next, let’s break it down next time
Don't underestimate these two lines, it is enough to arouse the curiosity of many audiences
This is very helpful for sucking powder and increasing viewing volume
He also learned it. I boast that his two sentences are purely objective facts, and they have no meaning of passing people by.
If you have any unpleasant people or things, please leave a message below
I'll help you scold him, I scold people who never carry dirty words
Of course you are responsible for the accident, I pay for dinner
Hahaha...
[Beatbox]
If you like my video, remember to like, comment, share, and turn on the small bell by the way!
See you next time! Bye bye