Hey, What's Up! My TM is Xiao Cai, who is your TM?
You are welcome to tmd to tmd my tmd channel, Yeah!
The thing called money is omnipotent, and there is nothing that cannot be bought
Only things that cannot be afforded, so-called unavailable, are purely sour
Or chicken soup to comfort the loser
You will definitely refute in your heart that money cannot bring people back to life
This sentence is right on the surface, but in fact it is only half right
If it is a physical resurrection
Judging from the current technology, it is still in the experimental stage, and it is difficult to truly realize
But if you have money, you can continue to throw money to scientists to study this technology
And scientific research originally required the country to spend a lot of money on experiments
The purpose is to make more money in the market after the experiment is successful
If it is a spiritual resurrection, this can be done
Because the so-called death is forgotten
Then just let people remember someone
He will live in our hearts forever
This is easy to handle. More money is thrown to expose the media to this person’s life story.
Find some senior editors to beautify this person
As long as there is enough money and headlines every day, I don’t believe you will forget this person
You may also argue that money can’t make people who don’t love you fall in love with you
Then I want to ask you, where does the person who loves you love?
Is it purely attracted by your personal charm?
The assumption is, what is your personal charm?
Is it your talent? Still rely on the money you have earned?
Obviously it’s the money you earn from falling in love with your talents.
You would say that girls look for boys, not just money
Also depends on appearance, height, way of speaking, temper
Waiting for harsh conditions is actually secondary
As long as money is in place, everything is in place
Ugly looks, go for a facelift, the height is bruised
If it is outstanding in other aspects, it can be made up
It’s hard to speak, it doesn’t matter
The main thing is to take her out to eat, go shopping, watch movies,
If you drive a sports car to the door
Say: Hi, take you out to play? What is there to say?
What do you say if you have a weird temper and a discordant personality?
Look at the men on the rich list, which is not a neuropathy
Which is not divorced several times?
But does anyone say they are neurotic? No
People will only say: hello has connotation, you are so detached!
Those who have no money will only be scolded and sick, this is the reality
So you have to make more money, just have money, everything else is secondary
What else do you think money can't buy?
For example, buy the earth?
There is nothing wrong with this, the present owner of the earth is now human
You have to dominate the planet and be the boss now
There must be a war, whether it can be won, 99% depends on the weapon
Weapons are bought with money. Obviously, the more expensive the weapon, the more advanced
Then you can buy all the most advanced weapons of humanity
Isn't this where nobody can beat you? Isn't it?
You might also say that money can't buy time.
This sentence looks fine on the surface, but it is out of place in reality
I just want to ask you, did you make a lot of time for the money you made at work?
And the salary the company pays you is equivalent to buying your time with money
You are selling your life, life is time
Then you pay for food, drink and fun, did you buy someone else's time?
Others are selling his time, you are enjoying the time in exchange for money
You said that I am clearly enjoying the material life?
But the essence of matter is time, your movement in space
Is the trace left by time
If you can’t understand it, just let it go, anyway, the material and time in my eyes are the same thing
Money is more than the numbers in your mobile wallet
It is essentially a symbol of value, so it is called a general equivalent
I’m not teaching you here, I’m just mentioning common sense.
How to make money? Let's not mention making big money, are you worthy?
Let's start with making small money, such as street food:
Brother, I would like the hot duck duck intestine
He spent two minutes to do it for you, you gave him a dozen dollars
Why can he make money? Because it's delicious! It's that simple
Solve the needs of a class of people
Why did he make small money?
So many people like to eat teppanyaki duck intestines.
Because of the fierce competition, it’s not just his family that sells
Yishan is higher than Yishan, who makes delicious food, who makes money
Of course, those geographical locations and other natural reasons are not my concern
This is a good decision they have considered before doing business
On the other hand, if you don’t make it, you won’t make money.
Or you can't make ends meet, any industry has enough to eat and support
I can’t eat enough and starve to death, so I’m doing the same thing. I’m eliminated without core competitiveness.
Let's talk about making big money, or just the example just now, what kind of thinking is the person making small money?
I want to make my own food the best
I want to let more people know that my food is the best
What is the idea of ​​the big money maker? I want to open more branches
I want more people to join our store, I want to build my own brand
I want to monopolize this market, I want to let my peers have no food to eat, and finally I am annexed
This is the essential difference, a gap on the ideological level
Of course, just thinking without action is empty talk
The reality is still cruel, not so easy to succeed
You can think of ways to make money
What to do, I had to have some personal characteristics while imitating others
Besides, the iron duck intestines just now, so many people are selling
I have to be different from others, so I have to develop some exclusive formulas
Others can't imitate it, and then experiment
Take a look at the most popular formula. After the experiment is successful, keep making it.
At the same time, optimize the service to give customers a better experience
Why don’t those who work hard make money because those who make money don’t need to
Why am I saying so vaguely, I won't tell you
This is an industry secret, but I can also reveal a secret word to you:
Look at the leeks, cut a stubble, grow a stubble, grow fast! Hey!
In addition to the evil money, is there anything pure in the world?
I don’t want to be so profitable, I don’t want to be so material
I just want to be simple
Sorry, really not
Only evil money, so give me all evil money
Let me bear the sin alone
Give Me Your Money
Brany-money minimum Mini-mini-mini-mini minimum
When it comes to pure things, I think of the most pretentious words
The line in "Mermaid": If there is not even a drop of clean water in this world
No matter how much money you make, it's a dead end!
I just want to say: if there is no money, even the water plant can go bankrupt
Do you still drink clean water?
The rich are worthy of drinking clean water, and the poor are only worthy of drinking dirty water. This is the reality!
Not to mention the environmental protection industry
It doesn't need money any more. Without money, even a volunteer cannot recruit!
This line is not genuine in nature
Just to move the audience and earn more movie tickets
If you sincerely call on others to be environmentally friendly
So why are so many advertisements still being planted in the movie, isn't it for the purpose of making money?
Of course there is nothing wrong with it, I just used it as an example
Let's stop talking nonsense, let's go make money, it's all business...
It's all business...
[Buzz~hula~]
Rap time, please turn down the volume
Yeah!
This world is extremely unfair, ha~
This world is extremely unfair
He who works hard does not make money
Those who make money do not have to work hard
If you have money, you have no choice.
You are poor, you get out of here, you don't need your presence here~
No need for your presence here~Yeah~
Extremely unfair
[Beatbox]
Oh Money~
It's all business~
Hey~ Br~~~
You want money and death
Ask for money, how to live without money
Money is life, life is money
No life without money, no life without money
Oh, Money~
I give you money～
you give me life
you give me death
Ahha~
Caring for vulnerable groups, eh? does not exist
Are you bullying and weak? Ha~
I hate this world, this world hates me
I choose to be harmonious in the world
No choice, To be or Not To be
This is not a problem
Forever
[噔 噔噔噔噔]
I don't want this kind of life
Let's go to make money, it's all business~ Hey~
Stalling is a business
Let you set up your stall, let you plant your land, ha~
Are you a puppet? Is five dollars cool at a time? Eh!
Cottage is a business
I am a cottage, a cottage, you are a cottage, a cottage
No one loves cottages, who TM buys Xiaomier~ Hey!
Patriotic is a business, shouting that patriotism can attract fans
It sucks brain powder ah ei yeah br~
Foreigners are patriotic when licking their dogs.
Zhang Ze Beatbox True TM Patriotic
[Zip~]
Your Dick Not Big, Your Dick No ... Big
Pretending is a business, who are you pretending to show?
I really don’t want to see it, but you still show it to me
Love is a business
Want to eat with me, go shopping and watch movies
First, there is a house and a car
If you have money, you have no money to stand by. You are poor and you get out
F**k~ [buzz~hula]
Tourism is a business
Scenic spots are not yours, they are yours after you buy the ticket
If you have money, you have no money to stand by. You are poor and you get out
Rolling ~ AhHa~
Papa is a business, pornography
Everyday, there are live chickens in the village in the city
Live chickens, live chickens, every country has its national anthem, hey~
Meal is a business, please invite you to this meal
I'll ask for the next meal, or order a takeaway
Your mother called you home for dinner, hey Yeah Br~
I seem a bit hungry
eh, I forget something? aha?
My Dick Can Ate!
AAAA Ay-Ay-Ron Can Ate