Lose weight to lose weight, the more you lose, the more fat you lose. It's not about you, you can lose weight if you want to lose weight.
Are you still worrying about losing weight? Are you still worried about your weight?
Do you still want to eat but dare not eat?
Are you still turning the hula hoop? I know what you are thinking
Please keep reading. Don't worry, I'm not selling weight loss pills
I just have some weight loss experience and want to record an inner monologue about weight loss
Losing weight is not just by shouting, you have to shout every day
Countless people are doing fasting challenges. They can lose many kilograms without eating for a few days.
I have to say that as long as your willpower is strong enough, how much thinner you want to lose?
But don’t forget, the ideal is full, the reality is skinny
Not many people can stick to the end, and not many normal people stick to the end
Do you think it’s normal if you don’t eat one meal a month?
Personal physique, some people resist hunger, some people don’t resist hunger
I believe most people are the latter
Of course, anti-hunger requires training. The human stomach is flexible, but it can be large or small.
The stomach of people who resist hunger must be a big deal
You said that some big stomach kings don’t seem to be fat
That’s because he vomited in the toilet after eating, and didn’t let you see it.
So I want to say that if you want to lose weight, you have to shrink your stomach, and you will be full after eating a little.
Don’t forget that the ultimate goal of weight loss is to develop a lean body
Don’t gain weight by eating anything, eat what you like, don’t restrain yourself
Of course, to lose weight, you must go on diet or fasting training to ensure your health.
This is scientific
If it’s just to be thinner and thinner, compare with thinner
That will only hurt your body, not worth imitating
The ideal weight of a person is after calculating BMI
Determined according to the average level of your country
Setting goals blindly is unscientific, unhealthy, and unrealistic
Next I will talk about the pros and cons of dieting or fasting to lose weight
Before that, let me add a digression, no matter what way to lose weight
It’s liposuction, carnitine, exercise
More purpose is to look better
For men to show off their abdominal muscles, and for women to show off their long legs, they are more for others to see
What is healthy or unhealthy, not many people care about it before
Now more and more people care about this
Not only to be thin, but to be healthy and happy
If the process of losing weight is painful, it will be difficult to stick to it
Even if you persist, you will eventually become sickly thin
What's more, the ultimate goal of weight loss is not just to lose weight
Do you think about why you lose weight? Is it for the weight to stop rebounding?
Eat whatever you want
If you keep on dieting for a period of time, your weight will indeed drop
The process is also very painful
If one day you really can't control yourself
It’s easy to overeating, because I’ve been holding back for so long
At this time, the rebound speed will be very fast, and the weight loss will be lost.
So I just rely on will to lose weight
No sustainable development. Because people’s desire is greater than their will, they have to go with the flow.
You are not a monk, and you are not a ninja, so there is no need for such painful restraint of desire
Intermittent fasting + moderate exercise is currently one of the mainstream scientific ways to lose weight
To put it bluntly, it means to shut your mouth and open your legs
But it’s relatively harder to stick to it, because it may take several days without eating
For people who are accustomed to three meals a day, they are hungry without eating, let alone for several days
So it’s a scientific, effective and easy way to lose weight, I personally think it’s one meal a day
In fact, many people have mentioned this way in the video
It’s just that I have some opinions of my own, which are different from them
One meal a day not only satisfies the appetite, but also achieves the goal of dieting and weight loss, while saving a lot of time
If you want to stick to one meal a day, you still need a gradual process
I have a plan here that can adapt to one meal a day for people who have three meals a day
Start with two meals a day, and eat every meal.
Actually it’s like most people don’t eat breakfast, it’s not difficult
After getting used to it, reduce food intake and eat seventy percent full for every meal
At this time, I feel a little hunger every day
When you are hungry, you can reduce hunger by distracting
The easiest is to play with the phone, the whole day passed
When you are really hungry, drink a sugar-free drink or skim milk
It’s not difficult to hold your stomach, when your body adapts
Continue to reduce food intake. Or two meals a day
This process will be a little bit painful, but not particularly difficult
Soon your body will adapt, when your body adapts
Your stomach shrinks a bit, and you’re full after eating a little
Don’t worry about malnutrition
The nutrients stored in your body are enough for you to use for a month or two
Unless you are already malnourished, I believe there are not many people who are malnourished who need to lose weight.
Malnutrition and losing weight is death
Of course the situation I’m talking about here excludes some puffy people
The main reason they are fat is that they eat too much junk food
Even if you are fat, you may be malnourished
Can you eat junk food instead of regular meals during the diet?
It’s okay, it’s just unhealthy, no one stops you if you have to eat
Anyway, as long as you eat less, you can lose weight. When your appetite decreases
One meal a day seems very relaxing, but don’t be too happy
There is still some way to lose weight
Because the state at this time is unstable, you may resume three meals a day at any time
It has even become more edible than before, after all, I have been holding back for so long. So the solution is
Raise the goal a bit higher, one meal every two days
This meal must be fully eaten, otherwise it will be difficult to persist
And the nutrition should be comprehensive, snacks are not good
In order to prevent malnutrition, it is best to eat some vitamins, such as a good pill after a meal
Why do you have to eat once every two days? This is to make you more resistant to hunger and last longer
When you think it’s not difficult to have one meal in two days, resume one meal a day plan
At this time you will feel that one meal a day is no different from three meals
It’s normal, without any psychological pressure, it’s natural
As the saying goes
If your goal from start to finish is one meal a day
It will be more difficult for you to persist because your body’s adaptability has not yet reached this level
It’s like having someone who never exercises do push-ups
He couldn't do one at first, but after training, he can finally do one
But after a period of time, let him do it again, it will be very difficult for him, and he can’t even do one.
If this person’s initial goal is to do ten, then his training difficulty and intensity will be higher
After a long time, let him do one more, he will feel very relaxed
So, the one meal plan is not as simple as you think
The most important thing is long-term persistence, which does not count as one or two days.
Compared with a thorough fasting to lose weight, the effect of losing weight with one meal a day will be slower
The degree of pain is much smaller, there is almost no pain after adapting
Fasting to lose weight is different. You can’t eat for two or three days, you can only drink a little water
Not much harm to the body in a short time, and no malnutrition
But after a long time, it will definitely hurt, at least it will have low blood sugar.
Like those who are still energetic without eating for days, most of them are fitness coaches.
At the same time, they are a bit fat, they are very resistant to hunger, and their metabolism is much faster than ordinary people.
Fat consumption rate is also higher, scientific fasting time is 72 hours
Exceeding this time may cause organ failure
Of course it’s not so absolute, this is an average
Some people just resist hunger. The process is painful during fasting or dieting
Remember not to watch food shows, this will make you hungry more and more, and you can’t even control yourself
You can lose weight without eating, does that mean you can lose weight without eating?
Is it possible to fast for a while and refresh for a while?
This is the theory, but the reality is the opposite
This may starve to death, but before starving to death, most people choose to eat
Because this is the instinct of carbon-based organisms
The order in which the human body consumes energy is sugar, fat, and protein
But never consume protein after the fat is 100% exhausted
This is why people who starve to death also have a lot of fat
Because consuming fat also needs fat, he doesn’t even have fat to consume fat
Then it can only consume muscle. And consuming muscles also requires a lot of energy
He doesn’t even have the most basic energy to sustain life, so he can only starve to death
This is equivalent to the phone is dead and automatically shut down
At the same time, I also answered the sentence: How can I lose weight without eating?
Share my experience of intermittent fasting
The first time I fasted, I lost 8 catties of meat in 4 days
Drink only one box of yogurt every day, do fat burning exercises, and measure your weight on a scale every day
On average, I can lose about 1 kilogram a day, very effective
In the end, the reason why I couldn’t keep going was because there were snacks around, I couldn’t help it.
After eating snacks, I never want to endure this kind of suffering and pain anymore
Return to normal diet. You will ask, are you hungry?
I’m hungry, but I’m not very hungry. I can bear it. This is unexpected.
Not hungry enough to growl. May be the reason for drinking yogurt
The pain I am talking about is not physical pain, everything is normal in the body
What I’m talking about is that you have to control yourself not to eat if you have food around you. This psychological torture is painful
I lost 16 pounds of meat in 10 days on the second fast
I originally planned to lose 40 pounds of meat a month, and then my future life depends on
One meal a day, one high-quality meal a day, to maintain your weight
The result was defeated by reality. In the early morning of the 11th day, I was hungry and woke up, not a nightmare. Was awakened from starvation alive
Because I felt very hungry before I went to bed on the 10th night
But I told myself that if I persisted for a few more days
I woke up after only two hours of sleep
After waking up, my heart beats faster and I feel like I'm going to die
It’s like Ultraman’s red light, can’t hold on anymore
I hurriedly frozen the rice that I cooked half a month ago in the refrigerator and took out all of it and put it in the microwave
I made another meal by the way, which is equivalent to eating three meals in one meal
But I'm full before I finish eating because my stomach shrinks
Although I did not stick to the end and did not lose weight successfully, it was effective anyway
My appetite has decreased a lot, and I can be full with just a little bit
For these 10 days, I rely on drinking fruit juice, yogurt, sugar-free beverages, without a little fat intake
There is a small amount of sugar, sugar will quickly turn into fat
In order to reduce the fat conversion rate, do a little fat burning exercise every day
Do very little, worry about running out of strength today, and unable to recover tomorrow
I feel a little more dizzy compared to eating
Because of short-term hypoglycemia, my body has not adapted to it
But my strength is not weakened, the same as those who exercised during fasting said
I believe that when your hunger reaches a certain level, you must go back and take the initiative to eat
Desire will defeat your will
This is not the age of famine, this is the age of over-nutrition, so I have to lose weight
Are those who do fasting challenges really not hungry? the answer is negative
They must be hungry, so why do some people say that they don’t feel hungry at all without eating for a week?
He was hungry and numb. For example, surgery, anesthetics
It was very painful at first, but after taking the anesthetic, you don’t feel very painful anymore
At this time, you say that cutting meat doesn't hurt at all. Do you think it's appropriate?
He said there is no hunger, it means that you can distract
To forget about hunger, it’s not a real sense of hunger
Humans are made of meat, not machines, just charge it up
But it’s not as hungry as imagined. The human body is adaptive.
Originally, you are not hungry. After a period of time, your body adapts
That little bit of hunger is trivial
At this time he can say: I am not hungry at all
Pain will make you stronger. Of course everything has to be scaled
Fasting training for a long time is harmful to the body
May be malnourished, so vitamins and trace elements should be added in time
In the absence of food intake, the food in the body is exhausted
The body produces an autophagy effect. In addition to fat, it will consume
Skipping meals will speed up the metabolism and make people more energetic in a short time, but eating will make you sleepier
Why do people have fat and grow small belly
Because primitive people eat irregularly, the last meal may not be the next
So every meal has to eat as much as possible, excess energy, no place to store
So fats that can store energy for longer have evolved
It’s more exciting the next time you hunt
The rate of fat consumption is relatively slow, and it is not enough to lose weight by skipping meals
Also do delayed fat burning exercise, delayed fat burning exercise is not like aerobic exercise
It takes 30 minutes to consume fat. Of course, this is just a reference number, and I can’t believe it all.
Delay fat burning, only need to do about five or six minutes of training, you can burn fat
Even if you stop exercising and start to rest, you will continue to burn fat
Until the body cools down and stops sweating. Like poppy jumping, pull-ups, variable speed running, boxing, etc.
For girls, you can choose a relatively relaxed aerobic exercise
Like jumping and jogging
If you exercise regularly and these are not difficult for you, then you can choose higher intensity training
Delaying fat burning exercise is equivalent to simmering in flames, and you can’t enjoy the joy of exercise
Only endless pain can be used to vent emotions, the advantage is obvious: save time
Aerobic exercise is like simmering in a small fire, slow work and careful work, you can enjoy the happiness brought by exercise
The disadvantage is obvious: it is time-consuming. Choose according to personal preference
After talking about one meal a day, let’s talk about three meals a day. Its historical origin
In ancient times, people had two meals a day, one meal when they went out to work in the morning, and another one when they returned home from work in the afternoon.
No food at night, no electricity, no entertainment, only lying down and sleeping
Sometimes there is a curfew at night, no door is given
I can only hear the eunuch shouting outside: The sky is dry and everything is dry, watch out for the fire
During the Song Dynasty, the night market was opened, so you can go out at night and go shopping and shopping.
The people of the Song Dynasty were prosperous, and two meals were too small
I have nothing to do at night, so I might as well cook something, so three meals a day became popular
If the civilian life of the Song Dynasty is really as luxurious as the legend, eating, drinking, having fun, and ordering takeaway
Finally, I will mention the dieting technique, which is to reduce appetite. When do you not want to eat?
Eat something bad, but some bad things are nutritious
To reduce my appetite in the past, I accidentally found that protein powder was really awful
But it’s very nutritious. After a drink, I don’t want to eat all day. It’s really effective.
But it was so uncomfortable, I finally had to give up
Let’s say so much today, I wish you all weight loss success